[
  {
    "front": "ア",
    "back":  "a"
  },
  {
    "front": "イ",
    "back":  "i"
  },
  {
    "front": "ウ",
    "back":  "u"
  },
  {
    "front": "エ",
    "back":  "e"
  },
  {
    "front": "オ",
    "back":  "e"
  },
  {
    "front": "カ",
    "back":  "ka"
  },
  {
    "front": "キ",
    "back":  "ki"
  },
  {
    "front": "ク",
    "back":  "ku"
  },
  {
    "front": "ケ",
    "back":  "ke"
  },
  {
    "front": "コ",
    "back":  "ko"
  },
  {
    "front": "サ",
    "back":  "sa"
  },
  {
    "front": "シ",
    "back":  "shi"
  },
  {
    "front": "ス",
    "back":  "su"
  },
  {
    "front": "セ",
    "back":  "se"
  },
  {
    "front": "ソ",
    "back":  "so"
  },
  {
    "front": "タ",
    "back":  "ta"
  },
  {
    "front": "チ",
    "back":  "chi"
  },
  {
    "front": "ツ",
    "back":  "tsu"
  },
  {
    "front": "テ",
    "back":  "te"
  },
  {
    "front": "ト",
    "back":  "to"
  },

  {
    "front": "ナ",
    "back":  "na"
  },
  {
    "front": "ニ",
    "back":  "ni"
  },
  {
    "front": "ヌ",
    "back":  "nu"
  },
  {
    "front": "ネ",
    "back":  "ne"
  },
  {
    "front": "ノ",
    "back":  "no"
  },
  {
    "front": "ハ",
    "back":  "ha"
  },
  {
    "front": "ヒ",
    "back":  "hi"
  },
  {
    "front": "フ",
    "back":  "fu"
  },
  {
    "front": "ヘ",
    "back":  "he"
  },
  {
    "front": "ホ",
    "back":  "ho"
  },
  {
    "front": "マ",
    "back":  "ma"
  },
  {
    "front": "ミ",
    "back":  "mi"
  },
  {
    "front": "ム",
    "back":  "mu"
  },
  {
    "front": "メ",
    "back":  "me"
  },
  {
    "front": "モ",
    "back":  "mo"
  },
  {
    "front": "ヤ",
    "back":  "ya"
  },
  {
    "front": "ユ",
    "back":  "yu"
  },
  {
    "front": "ヨ",
    "back":  "yo"
  },

  {
    "front": "ラ",
    "back":  "ra"
  },
  {
    "front": "リ",
    "back":  "ri"
  },
  {
    "front": "ル",
    "back":  "ru"
  },
  {
    "front": "レ",
    "back":  "re"
  },
  {
    "front": "ロ",
    "back":  "ro"
  },
  {
    "front": "ワ",
    "back":  "wa"
  },
  {
    "front": "ヲ",
    "back":  "wo"
  },
  {
    "front": "ン",
    "back":  "n"
  },
  {
    "front": "ガ",
    "back":  "ga"
  },
  {
    "front": "ギ",
    "back":  "gi"
  },
  {
    "front": "グ",
    "back":  "gu"
  },
  {
    "front": "ゲ",
    "back":  "ge"
  },
  {
    "front": "ゴ",
    "back":  "go"
  },
  {
    "front": "ザ",
    "back":  "za"
  },
  {
    "front": "ジ",
    "back":  "ji"
  },
  {
    "front": "ズ",
    "back":  "zu"
  },
  {
    "front": "ゼ",
    "back":  "ze"
  },
  {
    "front": "ゾ",
    "back":  "zo"
  },
  {
    "front": "ダ",
    "back":  "da"
  },
  {
    "front": "デ",
    "back":  "de"
  },
  {
    "front": "ド",
    "back":  "do"
  },
  {
    "front": "バ",
    "back":  "ba"
  },
  {
    "front": "ビ",
    "back":  "bi"
  },
  {
    "front": "ブ",
    "back":  "bu"
  },
  {
    "front": "ベ",
    "back":  "be"
  },
  {
    "front": "ボ",
    "back":  "bo"
  },
  {
    "front": "パ",
    "back":  "pa"
  },
  {
    "front": "ピ",
    "back":  "pi"
  },
  {
    "front": "プ",
    "back":  "pu"
  },
  {
    "front": "ペ",
    "back":  "pe"
  },
  {
    "front": "ポ",
    "back":  "po"
  }
]
